back in the times of Ancient Rome there was such a
ещё времён Древнего Рима был такой
principle Yes, that a slave is not
принцип Да что раб не несёт
responsible for the affairs of his
ответственности за дела своего
master Alice continue, I’m
хозяина Алиса продолжай я из города
from the city of Khmelnitsk Where are you from? We’re from Russia, I understand, let’s talk normally Come on, come on Alice stop How are you, conductor Kato I’m from
стоп Как дела вас дирижёр Като Я из
the city of Khmelnitsk Where are we from  from Russia, the
города Хмельницке Вы откуда Мы из России
city of Smolensk, what an
город Смоленск вот Город какой
interesting city Smolensk would be, Smolensk, and what you
интересной бы Смоленск Смоленск а чем
communicate
общаетесь
here, I don’t know, we want to talk to you Well,
тут не знаю хочем поговорить с вами Ну
let’s not talk about war or
давайте не о войне и не
politics How are you doing? Wait, I’m talking,
политике Как у вас дела Подожди я говорю
let’s not talk about neither about politics Okay
давайте нени О воне ни о политике Окей
Well, it’s easy for us, no problem  now
Ну это без проблем нам просто сейчас
I got one, Come on Let someone not in the
попался один та Давай Пусть кто не в
frame speak. It turns out that I’ll
кадре не говорит Балаган получается я
just switch it. Come on. You’re in the frame and
просто переключу Давайте Вот вы в кадре
then you say. Let him not scream
вы тогда и говорите Пусть он не кричит
from the side, there’s someone from the side screaming without any problems,
сбоку там кто сбоку кричит без проблем
just a microphone, I’ll just look, I’ll say right away
просто микрофон я просто смотрите сразу
that
скажу да что
we don’t have to  to you ordinary Russians
мы не имеем к вам простым россиянам
We
Никаких претензий мы
understand no complaints, don’t [ __ ] here Many don’t understand,
понимаем не сри у нас Многие не понимают
but I preach this thesis among Ukrainians
но я проповедуют среди украинцев вот эту
that, as it were, with you, ordinary
тези что как бы вот ещё ж с вы ж простые
people, nothing depends on you Truth Well,
люди от вас ничего не зависит Правда Ну
Putin attacked, he decided since the time of
Путин напал он решил ещё со врем
Ancient Rome  such a principle Yes, that a
Древнего Рима был такой принцип Да что
slave is not responsible for the affairs of
раб не несёт ответственности за дела
his master, that is, therefore, we
своего хозяина то есть Поэтому мы не
cannot blame you for
можем вас обвинять в
the fact that you somehow influenced Yes, you had a
мто вы как-то влияли Да на У вас был
president who you elect, if you influenced
президент который вы избирает влияли бы
him, then we would have something for you
на него да то мы бы к вам что-то имели
claim And if you are slaves in this country,
претензию А если вы рабы в этой стране
conquered
покорённый
Well, in short, you have a good policy And
Ну короче у тебя хорошая политика А
why are you sitting in front of the flag of
почему ты сидишь на фоне флага
Ukraine And why are you sitting in front of the flag of
Украины А почему ты на фоне флага
Ukraine Well, it’s clear that you are in this
Украины сидишь Ну понятно что ты в этой
country Why so directly propagandize
стране Зачем так прямо пропагандировать
that you live in this country And why
что ты в этой стране живёшь А чем тебя
I’m also stressing you out with the trident here, I’m
напрягаю я ещё и с тризубом тут нем
just wondering why I like it, I
просто интересно зачем мне нравится мне
like sitting against the background of the flag, so I get
нравится сидеть на фоне флага вот я
a kick out of it, but you’re sitting against the background of the
кайфую от этого вот ты же сидишь на фоне
curtain. I’m not saying that you sat there against the
шторы Я же не говорю что ты там сел на
background. What, well, these are slightly different things.
фоне Что Да ну это немного разные вещи
Well  how slightly different everyone sits, but I
Ну как немного разные каждый сидит вот я
didn’t tell you that you have a cutout
же тебе не придал что у тебя там вырез
like this or not, everyone sits with whatever they want,
такой или не такой каждый с чем хочет
the question is Why does this
тем и сидит вопрос Почему тебя это
bother you? Yes, I’m just interested. It does
тревожит Да мне просто интересно Меня
n’t matter to me. That’s why you
это никак не Вот почему тебя
were interested in the
заинтересовал именно
flag. It wasn’t the flag that interested you.  Ukraine
флаг Меня заинтересовал не флаг Украины
And the fact that you are sitting in front of the flag Well, that's
А то что ты на фоне флага сидишь Ну
right Because if you look I
Правильно Потому что если смотри я
put Why did I put a flag behind me
поставил Почему я поставил сзади себя
yes yes Because if I put a
флаг да да Потому что если бы я поставил
flag in front of me you wouldn't
спереди себя флаг ты бы меня не
see me that Well it's logical Well what are your
видела что Ну логично Ну какие у тебя
hobbies
хобби есть
chess good  you play a little hello how
шахматы хорошо играешь немножко алло как
long ago from the fourth grade
давно с четвёртого класса
professionally to the eleventh grade
профессионально по одиннадцатый класс
Then you didn’t play seriously well anymore,
Потом больше уже не играл серьёзно
but whatever you want in chat roulette
а сам что хочешь в чат рулетки
conversations
разговоров бы
I would like it’s
я это
my research
исследовательские у меня
motives, it’s just that in fact it
мотивы просто на самом деле меня это
surprised me that you
удивило то что ты прям открыто
so openly expressed your position  about the fact that
так высказал свою позицию по поводу что
you don’t have any aggression towards us,
у тебя нет никакой агрессии к нам
let them in with you, they Zhenya
впуска с вами би они Жени на что не
couldn’t influence what they were powerless slaves
могли повлиять они бесправные раб были
Well, there were no complaints against them That
Ну и к ним Никаких претензий не было То
is, if there were some
есть если было каких-то
two, it’s like the slave owners are quarreling with themselves
два как бы рабовладельца с собой
and they have  claims to each other
ссорятся да у них претензии друг к другу
But not to each other’s slaves, you
Но не к рабам друг друга понимаешь
just understand the world of evolution, many of them
просто мир эволю многие нде
went through feudalism there and now they are
прошли там феодальные и сейчас вот
different. Well, most countries are
разные ро Ну большинство стран они
democratic. We, for example, in Ukraine, we
демократические Мы например в Украине мы
elected one president there; we don’t
выбрали там одного президента не
like it; we chose a second, then a
понравится выбрали второго потом
third And so on Yes, we understand  that
третьего И так дальше Да мы понимаем что
you are in your own country Yes, you were born, you
вы в своей стране Да вы родились вы её
didn’t choose it Yes, you didn’t choose to be born a
не выбирали Да вы не выбрали родиться
slave, there was no such thing as what you say God
рабом не было такого что вы говорите Бог
send me here I want to be short
пошли меня сюда Я хочу короче быть Вот
Here, there was no such thing as powerless in this country, it’s
тут бесправным в этой стране не было
true. How do you relate to people from Ukraine
правда А как ты относя людям из Украины
who  Well, they vehemently hate the common
которые Ну яро прям ненавидят и простой
people and, in general, the Russian military
народ и в целом военных русских
who attacked
которые напали на
Ukraine, not really, that is, it
Украину не совсем то есть
surprises you Why do people hate the
тебя удивляет Почему люди ненавидят
Russian military, no, it surprises me, it
российских военных нет меня удивляет
doesn’t even surprise me, I’m interested in them,
даже не удивляет Я интересу к ним
the Ukrainians who vehemently hate the Russians,
украинцам которые яро ненавидят русских
ordinary Russians, Russians or military,
простых русских Русских или военных ты
you say  don’t look at the military, well, with the
говори ты с военных не смотри ну с
military, everything is clearly necessary for the military And
военными всё однозначно военных надо И
everything is so that they Who will die, who will run away
всё да чтобы они Кто умрёт кто убежит
because they attacked our country is
потому что они напали на нашу страну
absolutely normal, everyone who hates the
абсолютно нормально все кто ненавидит
Russian military is handsome, yes, but everyone
российских военных красавчики да но все
who hates Russian slaves Yes,
кто ненавидит рабов российских Да вот
those who are not you, but just like that  they are slaves of the
которые не выт а просто вот они рабы
Russian Federation, many of us don’t
Российской Федерации у нас многие не
understand. I
понимает Я
preach the thesis that there is no need for aggression
проповедуют тезис что не нужно агрессии
towards slaves, so that is, slaves don’t
к рабам так то есть рабы они ничего не
decide anything. Well, they can’t influence
решают Ну и они не могут повлиять ни на
anything. Yes, you are aggressive,
что Да ты агрессирует
make him have his own chains, that’s
сделать у него свои цепи есть только и
all, yes  that is, he
всё как бы да то есть к военным да
is aggressive towards the military, yes, for example, but towards slaves,
агрессирует да например А вот к рабам
people like you. Well, what kind of claims can there be,
Таких как вы Ну какие могут быть
just not everyone understands everyone
претензии просто не все понимают все
thinks here in Ukraine. Many people think that
думают у нас в Украине Многие думают что
you in Russia also live in a
вы в России тоже живёте в
democratic society and you are responsible
демократическом общест и вы ответственны
for this war, you elected your
за эту войну вы избирали вашего
President, your government for example
президента ваше правительство например
yes Wait now we have a small rearrangement
Вот подожди сейчас у нас перестановка
Now for a second
Сейчас секунду
all our asses are on fire now now
всё задницы пригорели сейчас сейчас
wait I’ll
подожди
sit down So monitor Well yes It’s logical
присяду Так монитор А ну да Логично
move over no I’m not replanting just
подвинься не не пересаживаю просто
under everything is almost
под всё
ready
готово
So ​​you think Russian people are
поч То есть ты считаешь русских людей
slaves like that No well you said what  we are not
рабами так Нет ну ты сказал то что мы не
to blame for the fact that we were born in Russia,
виноваты в том что мы родились в России
it’s that
то что
you influence something in this country,
сл вы вы на что-то влияете в этой стране
you said
вы сказали
no, you consider yourself
нет это вы себя считаете
slaves, that is, it turns out that you are also a slave.
рабами То есть получается ты тоже раб
No, why do I decide in my country, I am
Нет почему я в своей стране решаю я
elected, I influence the authorities  the authorities on
избирают я влияю на власть власть от
my
моего
behalf just have problems with the sound and
именит просто со звуком у нас проблемы а
you are from the microphone Get up in everything you can
ты с микрофона Встань во всё можешь
repeat please once yes yes Everything is
повторить прошу раз раз да да Всё всё
fine I said get up from the microphone and everything
хорошо ещ сказа встань с микрофона и всё
became
стало
fine Yes I seem to be sitting normally
хорошо Да я вроде и так сижу нормально
everything Repeat please I couldn’t hear
всё Повтори пожалуйста не слышно было
you  Let
тебя
's repeat Shama What should I repeat for you? Well, here's
повторим Шама Что тебе повторить Ну вот
my last
последний последнее своё предложение
last sentence. I don't remember my last
последние я не помню своё последнее
sentence. It's sad. Why do you
предложение это печально Почему ты
think
считаешь
Rami? Let's start from the beginning. I don't consider
Рами давай начнём сначала я не считаю
Russians to be slaves. I consider people to be
русских рабами Я считаю вот я людей
those who do not depend on them;
считаю тех которые ничего от них не
their state considers them slaves.
зависит их государство их считаю рабами
that is, they are controlled and they do not elect
то есть ими управляют а они не избирают
power, I asked you, yes, with a girl,
власть я у тебя спросил да с девушкой
or are you deciding something in your country, you
или вы что-то решаете в своей стране вы
said no, that is, you are slaves, you
сказали нет ну то есть вы рабы вы себя
recognized yourself as such, and not me. I don’t know your
такими признали а не я Я же не зна тя
point of view, for example.  I don’t
точка зрения я вот например себя не
consider myself a slave, wait, come on,
считаю рабом подожди давай так от тебя
something in your country depends on you,
что-то в твоей стране зависит
yes, that is, it turns out that you are
да то есть то есть получается ты ты
to blame for the fact that Russia attacked
виноват в том что Россия напала на
Ukraine Well, at that moment, no, wait
Украину Ну на тот момент нет подожди ещё
again Look, you’re asking Does it depend on
раз Смотри ты спрашиваешь Зависит ли от
me now in my  look at something in the country,
меня сейчас в моей стране что-то смотри
so now it’s that Russia
давай так вот сейчас то что Россия
attacked Ukraine Yes, does it act on your behalf
напала на Украину Да она от твоего имени
or not
действует или нет
no And that is, you don’t control the
нет А то есть ты не управляешь
president
президентом
No I don’t control the president doesn’t
Нет не управляю президент тебя не
represent you no that’s it So you’re a slave yes
представляет нет всё Значит ты раб да ты
you admit it, but it turns out  you are also a
ты это признаёшь а получается ты тоже
slave No why Come on ask me
раб Нет почему Давай спрашивай меня
Similarly, you represent you represent
Аналогично ты представ ты представляешь
the interests of your country Yes, the president
интересы своей страны Да президент
represents my interests, I
представляет мои интересы я ему
delegate to him in the elections Yes, and like other
делегирую на выборах Да и как и другие
people, we are the people who are the source of
люди мы народ который есть источником
power, we delegate to the president, we
власти мы делегирую президенту мы
delegate to deputies, we delegate
делегирую депутатам мы делегирую
our powers and they  President President Zelensky speaks on
свои полномочия и они выступают от
our behalf on behalf of the people of
нашего имени от имени народа
Ukraine. Yes,
Украины президент президент Зеленский Да
all decisions are made on behalf of the people of
все решения они идут от имени народа
Ukraine, not just Zelensky. On what
Украины не просто вот Зеленский От чего
behalf does he act on behalf of the people of
имени он действует от имени народа
Ukraine? I am responsible for all
Украины Я несу ответственность за все
his decisions; I carried the decision
его решения я нес решение зано
further on for all presidents because  I am a
дальше за всех президентов потому что я
citizen, I am
гражданин я
elected by them that who is the president? This is the
избирают им что кто такой президент Это
person whom we all appointed Yes, so
человек которого мы все поставили Да
that he carries out our
чтоб он исполнял нашу
will, we give him this right to delegate for
волю мы ему делегировать дали это право
5 years there, it depends on us and we
на там 5 лет от нас это зависит и мы
decide to take him or not to take him,
решаем забрать его или не забрать
leave or take
оставить или взять
another If you don’t  decide nothing then you are
другого Если вы не решаете ничего то вы
slaves,
рабы
we are not fish
мы не рыбы
Yeah Well, this is an interesting position
Угу Ну это интересная позиция на самом
actually Well, it
деле Ну так и
is Well look at the World Cup What is the essence of uh
есть Ну смотри В ЧМ В чём суть ээ
democracy and here is slavery Yes in democracy
демократии и вот рабства Да в демократии
people elect uh power Yes they
люди избирают э власть Да они
authorize there probably for 5 years here
уполномочиваю там наверно на 5 лет вот
we are for you  we give such and such powers Yes, they
мы Вам даём такие такие-то полномочия Да
control the power and so on in the
контролируют власть и так дальше в
slaveholding yes it turns out you
рабовладельческом да получается у вас
have there or in some kind of dictatorship
есть там или в какой-то диктатуре
there is someone in power, no one
есть кто-то Во власти его никто не
elects him, no one appoints him, he is
избирает его никто не назначает он
not accountable to anyone Yes, but he can over
никому не подотчёте Да а он может над
you  do whatever you want, collect tribute from you
вами что угодно делать собирать с вас
in the form of taxes,
Дань в виде налогов
throw you somewhere else in another country
Да кидать вас куда-то там другую страну
and do whatever you want at all, you
и что угодно вообще делать вы ему ничего
won’t do anything to him, just
не сделаете вот просто
nothing. For example, we had a president
ничего У нас например был президент
who decided to try
такой который решил попробовать
to play around with dictatorship Yanukovych ran away to
поиграться в диктатуру Янукович убежал к
you because  we said no, we are not slaves,
Вам потому что мы сказали нет мы не рабы
we will not tolerate such an
мы не будем се терпеть такого
attitude, we cannot go out and beat
отношения у нас нельзя выходить и бить
people at rallies and disperse them because we
людей на митинги разгонять потому что мы
are the source of power in our country. Yes,
есть источником власти в нашей стране Да
we have the right to gather for peaceful
мы имеем право собираться на мирные
demonstrations to demand something and to
демонстрации требовать что-то да э
put pressure on the authorities for  about making
давить на власть для про принятие
some decisions or canceling some decisions
каких-то или отмену каких-то решений
because we are the people
потому что мы народ
Well, it turns out you hate the Russians
Ну получается ты ненавидишь россиян
who Slava voted for Putin there, I
которые Слава голосовали За Путина там я
don’t know at all, in general they voted for someone,
не знаю вообще в целом за кого-то
look smo So I hate the
голосовали смотри смо Итак я ненавижу
Russians who say that yes, it
россиян которые говорят что да типа
turns out I  I am responsible for this
получается Я несу ответственность за это
for the actions of my government I support and
за действия моей власти Я поддерживаю и
so on Yes, if you say that you do not
так дальше Да если ты говоришь что ты не
bear any responsibility Yes,
несёшь никакой ответственности Да от
nothing depends on you, then you
тебя ничего не зависит то ты
are not a person who expresses his
не есть человек который выражает свою
will Yes, you are a slave of this system of this
волю Да ты раб этой системы этого
president or whatever you have  it’s
президента или как он у вас там
called the tsar I don’t know the emperor,
называется царь Я не знаю император кто
anyone, yes, that is, to you Well, what kind of claims can there
угодно да то есть к тебе Ну какие могут
be against you?
быть к тебе
Well, they don’t turn out to be against me. Well, that’s why I’m saying.
получается Ну то есть я же говорю
It’s just that many of us in Ukraine
поэтому Просто у нас многие в Украине
put an equal sign to all
они ставят знак равенства ко всем
Russians, so they think that  you are
россиянам так они думают что вы
free It’s just that here in Ukraine everyone
свободные Просто у нас в Украине все
is used to it. Yes, we are free people and it’s
привыкли Да что Мы свободные люди и нам
difficult for us to understand,
сложно понять
maybe it’s ready and that’s why When
может быть подго и поэтому Когда
you go out to Roulette Why is everyone yelling at you
выходите в Рулетку Почему на вас Орут
because people think that you are
все потому что люди думают что вы
free, you live in a Democratic country
свободны живёте в Демократической стране
and this war depends on you and  That’s why they’re
и от вас зависит эта война и поэтому на
swearing at you right away. I recommend
вас ругаются вот сразу Я рекомендую
making a sign, but nothing depends on me right away
сделать табличку да сразу от меня ничего
and show it right away and will
не зависит и сразу показывать и будет
react calmly. First I’ll start,
реагировать сначала начну стартовать
then it doesn’t depend on anything in this country.
потом обя от ниче в этой стране не
I’m a powerless person here.
зависит Я бесправный здесь челове
Well, in general, how do you think the
Ну вообще как думаете чем закончится
military operation will end? How it will end  a military
военная операция Чем закончится военная
operation with the defeat of the Russian Federation
операция поражением Российской Федерации
by dividing it into, uh, a dozen different
разделением её на ээ десяток разных
states on a national basis, on a
государств по национальному признаку по
territorial basis and the liberation of the
территориальному признаку и освобождение
people of the Russian Federation from this
народа Российской Федерации от этого
slave yoke, there
рабского ярма
will be
будут
special training programs that will
специальные обучающие программы будут
teach people how to elect how to
людей учить Как нужно избирать как можно
monitor the actions of the authorities, then, as far as
мониторить действия власти потом как
possible, we will say the accountability of the authorities will be demanded
можно скажем отчётность власти требовать
like this  that is, they will teach Well, this
так то есть будут учить Ну это
will be a transitional period from
переходной такой будет период от
dictatorship to democracy, first there will
диктатуры к демократии сначала нужно
be a need for a population that did not know how to
будет ну население которое не знало как
live freely Yes, they will need to be
это жить свободно Да ему нужно будет
shown what mechanisms there are in a
показывать какие есть механизмы в
free state Yes, for example,
свободном государстве Да например
demonstration rallies For example,
митинги демонстрации Вот например будут
people from France will come There with  Ukraine
приезжать люди из Франции Там с Украины
from English, look here, for example,
с англи вот смотрите у нас например
if you don’t like macron’s actions there Yes
если не нравятся там действия макрона Да
People come out for example To a rally Yes To a
Люди выходят например На митинг да На
rally for a demonstration and that’s normal
митинг на демонстрацию и это нормально с
Boris Johnson will come from Britain I’ll tell you from
Британии приедет Борис Джонсон там
which city from Smolensk from
с какого города со Смоленска со
Smolensk I can Smolensk by the way
Смоленска вот я може смолен кстати
not far from the Belarusians  let's come together
недалеко с белорусами вместе да приедем
Then after Belarus also
Потом после того как Белорусь тоже
give lectures in Smolensk Yes, methods of
проведу лекции в Смоленске Да методы
influencing local authorities For example,
влияния на местную власть Например у
I have experience Yes of
меня есть опыт
different companies at the level of my
Да разных компаний на уровне своего
city that we will teach everything to be normal, the main thing is to
города что научим всё нормально главно
defeat this announcer's hydra and everything
победить вот эту гидру дикторскую и всё
will be fine VS Let's not
будет хорошо ВС Давайте не будем
Well
Ну
let's have a blast I love to
давай кайф Я люблю такие
write such conversations Like it, please
разговоры пишиться Поставьте лайк
leave a comment for this Obvyazkovo so that this
залиште комент це обовязково чтоб це
video I can show more and more people Yes, we
видео побачу бильше и бильше людей Да мы
don't convey such
пон доноси такие
thoughts, I
думки кайфанул
got high Yes, damn it, that's all for the dude Divi, my
Да блин ну всё чуваку обес Диви моя
position is like this Yes, who from Russia
позиция такая Да кто нас из России
listens to us, why do they say that's a mouse
слушает ну почему они говорят вот мышь
it doesn’t depend on me, it doesn’t
это от меня не зависит от меня не
depend on me, yes, if it doesn’t depend on you, then you are a slave. You
да если от тебя не зависит то ты раб Ты
must understand this for yourself;
должен для себя это понять от тебя
nothing depends on you. That is, you are a human being,
ничего не зависит То есть ты человек бе
but if something depends on you, then it
а если от тебя что-то зависит да тогда
means they are rightfully yelling at you.
значит на тебя получается орут
Yes, and swearing write to you on my
правомерно Да и матюка тебя пись на мий
Telegram directly at once axis VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and even
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more video you don’t show to people at the moment you don’t
багато вдео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams for that for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that, for that we Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write directly  infection and bye there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm vdeo esh tezh tsikava and korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi vinni z you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write E
пиши E